O.W. Riegel Papers WLU.Coll.0387
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
O.W. Riegel Papers
1900-1992
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold)
Riegel, Hunt
WLU.Coll.0387
75 Linear Feet
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research use.
Biographical / Historical
Oscar Wetherhold Riegel, also known as Tom, was born in Reading, PA in 1903. Riegel's professional career began as a reporter and editor for the Chicago Tribune in the 1920s. He then shifted his focus to the information gathering and application, attaining a Bachelor's degree in the field from Dartmouth College and later attending Washington and Lee University.
Riegel became an internationally-known expert on the topic of propaganda in the 1930s after extensive studies of its importance in modern politics. His monograph, Mobilizing for Chaos: The Story of the New Propaganda, was published in 1934 and focused on the role propaganda was playing in the rise of National Socialism in Germany. In his studies he amassed an extensive collection of American, European, and Asian propaganda spanning World War I through the Cold War. Aspects of his compilation of propaganda studies are included within this collection. Riegel joined the Washington and Lee University Journalism Department in 1930 and was named department head in 1934. He served as department head until his retirement in 1973. During his tenure with the university, he taught various courses on film, journalism, propaganda, and information application. He passed away in 1997 in Lexington, VA.
Scope and Contents
Highlights of this collection include material concerning the Washington and Lee Journalism Department, including course material, student papers, and lecture notes. Supplementing this course material are published materials on the history of film, 20th century war propaganda, the Nazification of Germany, Paris in the 1920's and the "Lost Generation." There also includes wide selections of personal research materials for projects such as Riegel's books Mobilizing for Chaos and Crown of Glory; collections on Riegel's travels to Central and South America and Europe including Germany during the 1930s, and the typescript of his unpublished autobigraphy to 1945 titled "Hacking It."
Propaganda; Journalism; Riegel, Hunt
- Communication Satellites, 1962-1974; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 2.2 Linear Feet (Box 1-2, Folder 1-66)
  Scope and Contents
  Items in this series relate to news and developments in communications sattelites. Riegel wrote a short article about their impact on mass media. His manuscripts along with correspondence, reports, and publications about communications satellites make up the bulk of this series. Some items of note include reports on the progress of Canada's Telesat system, Riegel's analysis of satellite communication, and Comsat and Intelesat reports from the early 1970's
  Separated Materials
  There is one small box of assorted Newspaper Clippings related to Communication Sattelites, sorted by date (1962-1974) towards the end of the collection.
  Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1-8)
    Riegel discussed with over thirty correspondents over matters related to Communications Satellites and his academic article discussing the political barriers to satellite usage. Most correspondents provide suggestions to Riegel's article or explain how an academic journal they're associated with plans to use or not use his article.
    - Bar-de B, 1962-1974 (Folder 1)
    - Doy-Eig, 1962-1974 (Folder 2)
    - Gal-Mal, 1962-1974 (Folder 3)
    - Manuscript, 1962-1974 (Folder 4)
    - Mel-Pet, 1962-1974 (Folder 5)
    - Phi-Smo, 1962-1974 (Folder 6)
    - Smy-Wag, 1962-1974 (Folder 7)
    - Was-Yas, 1962-1974 (Folder 8)
  - Notes: European Satellites & Manuscript, 1962-1974 (Box 1 Communication Satellites, Folder 9)
  - Notes: ESRO, FCC, and Misc., 1962-1974 (Box 1 Communication Satellites, Folder 10)
  - Press Releases, 1962-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11-16)
    Press releases in this subseries mostly come from the COMSAT, INTELSAT, and TELESAT corporations. These press releases give reports on the developments in the satellite industry, and the changes in stock values for these companies' shareholders.
    - Press Releases, 1970-1972 (Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 1972-1973 (Folder 12)
    - Press Releases Mar.-Sep., 1973 (Folder 13)
    - Press Releases Oct.-Dec., 1973 (Folder 14)
    - Press Releases Jan.-Feb., 1974 (Folder 15)
    - Press Releases March, 1974 (Folder 16)
  - Publications, 1962-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17-31)
    Items in this subseries relate to pulbications from various sources refering to communications satellites. Items of note include: a Thesis titled, "Defense Department's usage of Communications Satellites" by Maurice Fliess from West Virginia University, annual COMSAT publications, and a Canadian publication on the ᐊᓂᒃ ("anik" or little brother)satellite by TELESAT.
    - Publications, 1962-1965 (Folder 17)
    - Publications, 1967 (Folder 18)
    - Publications, 1967-1968 (Folder 19)
    - Publications, 1969 (Folder 20)
    - Publications, 1969-1970 (Folder 21)
    - Publications, 1970-1971 (Folder 22)
    - Publications, 1971-1972 (Folder 23)
    - Publications, 1972 (Folder 24)
    - Publications Jan.-Jun., 1973 (Folder 25)
    - Publications Aug.- Nov., 1973 (Folder 26)
    - Publications, 1974 (Folder 27)
    - Publications Misc., 1962-1974 (Folder 28)
    - Publications Misc., 1962-1974 (Folder 29)
    - Publications Misc., 1962-1974 (Folder 30)
    - Publications Misc., 1962-1974 (Folder 31)
  - Reports, 1962-1974 (Box 1-2, Folder 32-60)
    Items in this subseries consist of reports by government and independent organizations about communication satellites. The reports vary in focus, ranging from technical data to impending impact of satellites on public life. Items of note include the 1972 Aeronautics and Space Report of the President and the operating agreement between the United States and other nations regarding INTELSAT.
    - Reports, 1964 (Folder 32)
    - Reports, 1966 (Folder 33)
    - Reports Jan., 1967 (Folder 34)
    - Reports Sep.-Nov., 1967 (Folder 35)
    - Reports, 1968 (Folder 36)
    - Reports, 1969 (Folder 37)
    - Reports Apr.-May, 1969 (Folder 38)
    - Reports Jul.-Sep., 1969 (Folder 39)
    - Reports Oct.-Nov., 1969 (Folder 40)
    - Reports Dec., 1969 (Folder 41)
    - Reports, 1970 (Folder 42)
    - Reports Jan., 1970 (Folder 43)
    - Reports Feb.-Mar., 1970 (Folder 44)
    - Reports Apr., 1970 (Folder 45)
    - Reports Jul.-Sep., 1970 (Folder 46)
    - Reports Sep., 1970 (Folder 47)
    - Reports Dec., 1970 (Folder 48)
    - Reports Feb.-May., 1971 (Folder 49)
    - Reports Aug., 1971 (Folder 50)
    - Reports, 1972 (Folder 51)
    - Reports, 1973 (Folder 52)
    - Reports, 1973 (Folder 53)
    - Reports Jan.-June, 1973 (Folder 54)
    - Reports Aug., 1973 (Folder 55)
    - Reports Aug. 31, 1973 (Folder 56)
    - Reports Sep.-Oct., 1973 (Folder 57)
    - Reports Dec., 1973 (Folder 58)
    - Reports, 1974 (Folder 59)
    - Reports Misc., 1962-1974 (Folder 60)
  - Riegel's Paper, 1962-1974 (Box 2, Folder 61-63)
    This subseries consists of Riegel's communication satellite article manuscripts. These manuscripts show the revisions Riegel made to his work.
    - Riegel's Paper Sep. 7th, 1970 (Folder 61)
    - Riegel's Paper June 11th, 1971 (Folder 62)
    - Riegel's Paper June 12th, 1971 (Folder 63)
  - Speeches, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Speeches, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Misc., 1962-1974 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Unprocessed Material, 1962-1974 (Box 2a)
    Items in this subseries are materials related to Riegel's work on Communication Satellites that have not yet been processed.
    Conditions Governing Access
    This part of the collection is not yet processed. Use of the collection is granted on a case by case basis. Please contact the Head of Special Collections at 540-458-8649 for more information.
- Dupont Awards, 1943-1982; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); Du Pont, Jessie Ball; Cole, Fred Carrington; Gaines, Francis Pendleton; 7.5 Linear Feet (Box 1-18, Folder 1-530)
  Items in this series are relevant to the Dupont Awards, which were given to Television stations, Radiostations, and commentators who have contributed to the field in their performance on the air. Award winners received $1,000, and most used the money to fund a journalism scholarship. Within this series are correspondence between award winners, judges, the Dupont estate, Washington and Lee University, members of the Federal Communications Commission, public relations firms, and O.W. Riegel, photographs of the award winners and annual awards dinner, publications by the Dupont Awards foundation, and published statements by various awards winners. Some items and subjects of note include a draft of a couple of the physical awards, letters discussing the conclusion of Washington and Lee's Association with the awards in 1967, and some resumes of different journalists and Judges' comments on various radio and television stations. Three scrapbooks are contained wtithin the collection, but are not in folders. They are listed in the appropriate sub-series. Major correspondents and speakers include: O. W. Riegel, FCC Chairman Rosel Hyde, and Jessie Ball Dupont.
  Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); Du Pont, Jessie Ball; Cole, Fred Carrington; Gaines, Francis Pendleton
  - American Association of University Women, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Announcement, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2-6)
    Items in this sub-series consist of materials describing the removal of Washington and Lee University from the administration of the Dupont Awards.
    - Bar-Cha, 1966-1967 (Folder 2)
    - Cole, 1966-1967 (Folder 3)
    - Hul-Sha, 1966-1967 (Folder 4)
    - Statement Drafts, 1966-1967 (Folder 5)
    - Official Statement, 1966-1967 (Folder 6)
  - Award, 1958-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7-14)
    Items in this subseries consist of correspondence, photos and cirtificates relating to types of awards given by institutions. Items of note include a small magazine of different award designs, correspondence over the dupont awards, and photographs of different awards.
    - Certificates, 1954-1964 (Folder 7)
    - Ack-Hol, 1954-1964 (Folder 8)
    - Lange, 1957-1961 (Folder 9)
    - Lange, 1962-1964 (Folder 10)
    - Lat-Mot, 1954-1964 (Folder 11)
    - Nel-Wen, 1954-1964 (Folder 12)
    - Photos, 1954-1964 (Folder 13)
    - Misc., 1954-1959 (Folder 14)
  - Booklet, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
    - Bot-Jah, 1951-1966 (Folder 15)
    - Joh-Wit, 1951-1966 (Folder 16)
  - Brochure, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 17-33)
    Items in this subseries primarily consist of correspondence related to the design of a brochure for the Dupont Awards. As the Awards' curator, Riegel was responsible for the Awrds' presentation and outreach.
    - A, 1951-1966 (Folder 17)
    - Bar-Bor, 1951-1966 (Folder 18)
    - Boswell, 1965 (Folder 19)
    - Boswell, 1965 (Folder 20)
    - Boy-Bus, 1951-1966 (Folder 21)
    - Cam-Cox, 1951-1966 (Folder 22)
    - Dar-Dow, 1951-1966 (Folder 23)
    - Duf-Dur, 1951-1966 (Folder 24)
    - E-F, 1951-1966 (Folder 25)
    - Gol-Gwa, 1951-1966 (Folder 26)
    - Hab-Hyd, 1951-1966 (Folder 27)
    - Joh-Loe, 1951-1966 (Folder 28)
    - Mah-Mon, 1951-1966 (Folder 29)
    - N-R, 1951-1966 (Folder 30)
    - Sim-Sur, 1951-1966 (Folder 31)
    - Tai-Vod, 1951-1966 (Folder 32)
    - Wad-Zap, 1951-1966 (Folder 33)
  - Critics, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 34-42)
    Items in this subseries consist of correspondents between Riegel and and individual reviewers the Dupont Awards. These letters consist of recommended radio stations that people felt deserved the award for 1963.
    - And-Cid, 1951-1966 (Folder 34)
    - Cle-Dwi, 1951-1966 (Folder 35)
    - Ech-Fre, 1951-1966 (Folder 36)
    - Gad-Hol, 1951-1966 (Folder 37)
    - Hul-Mol, 1951-1966 (Folder 38)
    - Mos-Sta, 1951-1966 (Folder 39)
    - Sub-Woo, 1951-1966 (Folder 40)
    - Remarks: Ced-Mac, 1951-1966 (Folder 41)
    - Remarks: Mar-Woo, 1951-1966 (Folder 42)
  - Awards Dinner, 1951-1966 (Box 2-5, Folder 43-129)
    Items in this sub-series consist of materials related to the Dupont Awards dinner including photographs, ivitations, and RSVP's.
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1951 (Folder 43)
    - Dinner Photos, 1951 (Folder 44)
    - Dinner Photos, 1951 (Folder 45)
    - Dinner Misc., 1951 (Folder 46)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1952 (Folder 47)
    - Dinner Photos, 1952 (Folder 48)
    - Dinner Misc., 1952 (Folder 49)
    - Dinner Materials, 1953 (Folder 50)
    - Dinner Photos, 1953 (Folder 51)
    - Dinner Photos, 1953 (Folder 52)
    - Dinner Photos, 1953 (Folder 53)
    - Dinner Materials, 1954 (Folder 54)
    - Dinner Materials, 1955 (Folder 55)
    - Dinner Materials, 1956 (Folder 56)
    - Dinner Photos, 1956 (Folder 57)
    - Dinner Photos, 1956 (Folder 58)
    - Dinner Materials, 1957 (Folder 59)
    - Dinner Photos, 1957 (Folder 60)
    - Dinner Photos, 1957 (Folder 61)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1958 (Folder 62)
    - Dinner Materials, 1958 (Folder 63)
    - Dinner Materials, 1958 (Folder 64)
    - Dinner Photos, 1958 (Folder 65)
    - Dinner Photos, 1958 (Folder 66)
    - Dinner Photos, 1958 (Folder 67)
    - Dinner Photos, 1958 (Folder 68)
    - Dinner Photos, 1958 (Folder 69)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1959 (Folder 70)
    - Dinner Materials, 1959 (Folder 71)
    - Dinner Materials, 1959 (Folder 72)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1960 (Folder 73)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1960 (Folder 74)
    - Dinner Materials, 1960 (Folder 75)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1961 (Folder 76)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1961 (Folder 77)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1961 (Folder 78)
    - Dinner Materials, 1961 (Folder 79)
    - Dinner Materials, 1961 (Folder 80)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1962 (Folder 81)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1962 (Folder 82)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1962 (Folder 83)
    - Dinner Materials, 1962 (Folder 84)
    - Dinner Materials, 1962 (Folder 85)
    - Dinner Photos, 1962 (Folder 86)
    - Dinner Photos, 1962 (Folder 87)
    - Dinner Photos, 1962 (Folder 88)
    - Dinner Photos, 1962 (Folder 89)
    - Dinner Photos, 1962 (Folder 90)
    - Dinner Photos, 1962 (Folder 91)
    - Requests, 1962 (Folder 92)
    - Misc., 1962 (Folder 93)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1963 (Folder 94)
    - Dinner Materials, 1963 (Folder 95)
    - Dinner Materials, 1963 (Folder 96)
    - Dinner Photos, 1963 (Folder 97)
    - Misc., 1963 (Folder 98)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1964 (Folder 99)
    - Dinner Materials, 1964 (Folder 100)
    - Dinner Materials, 1964 (Folder 101)
    - Dinner Materials, 1964 (Folder 102)
    - Dinner Photos, 1964 (Folder 103)
    - Misc., 1964 (Folder 104)
    - Misc., 1964 (Folder 105)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 106)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 107)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 108)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 109)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 110)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 111)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 112)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 113)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 114)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 115)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1965 (Folder 116)
    - Dinner Materials, 1965 (Folder 117)
    - Dinner Materials, 1965 (Folder 118)
    - Misc., 1965 (Folder 119)
    - Dinner Correspondence, 1966 (Folder 120)
    - Dinner Materials, 1966 (Folder 121)
    - Dinner Materials, 1966 (Folder 122)
    - Dinner Photos, 1966 (Folder 123)
    - Misc., 1966 (Folder 124)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1951-1966 (Folder 125)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1951-1966 (Folder 126)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1951-1966 (Folder 127)
    - Misc.Materials, 1951-1966 (Folder 128)
    - Misc. Dinner Photos, 1951-1966 (Folder 129)
  - Finances, 1951-1966 (Box 5, Folder 130-134)
    Items in this subseries consist of the financial documents Riegel dealt with for the Dupont Awards. Items of note include letters with the awards' finanical statements and individual bills for expenses.
    - Finances, 1951-1952 (Folder 130)
    - Finances, 1953-1960 (Folder 131)
    - Finances, 1961-1962 (Folder 132)
    - Finances, 1962-1964 (Folder 133)
    - Finances, 1964-1966 (Folder 134)
  - Forms, 1950-1982 (Box 5, Folder 135-138)
    Items in this subseries relate to forms used by the Dupont Awards committee. Some forms of note include blank radio station judging forms and form letters to nominees and participants.
    - Blank, 1950-1982 (Folder 135)
    - Letters: Ber-Jac, 1950-1982 (Folder 136)
    - Letters: Kal-Van, 1950-1982 (Folder 137)
    - Stock Letters, 1950-1965 (Folder 138)
  - General Correspondence, 1951-1966 (Box 6-8, Folder 139-238)
    Riegel's correspondence in this series is primarily between different awards administrators and judges. Riegel corresponded with approximately 320 different individauls within this subseries. Correspondents of note include Mrs. Dupont, Turner Catledge, and Sol Taishoff.
    - A, 1951-1966 (Folder 139)
    - Ban-Bea, 1951-1966 (Folder 140)
    - Bel-Boe, 1951-1966 (Folder 141)
    - Boy-Bro, 1951-1966 (Folder 142)
    - Cal, 1951-1966 (Folder 143)
    - Catledge, 1954-1958 (Folder 144)
    - Catledge, 1959-1961 (Folder 145)
    - Catledge, 1961-1962 (Folder 146)
    - Catledge, 1962-1964 (Folder 147)
    - Catledge, 1964-1967 (Folder 148)
    - Cha-Coh, 1951-1966 (Folder 149)
    - Cole, 1959-1961 (Folder 150)
    - Cole, 1962-1967 (Folder 151)
    - Col-Cou, 1951-1966 (Folder 152)
    - Cow-Cut, 1951-1966 (Folder 153)
    - Del-Dun, 1951-1966 (Folder 154)
    - Dupont, 1951-1952 (Folder 155)
    - Dupont, 1952-1953 (Folder 156)
    - Dupont, 1953-1954 (Folder 157)
    - Dupont, 1954 (Folder 158)
    - Dupont, 1954-1955 (Folder 159)
    - Dupont, 1955 (Folder 160)
    - Dupont, 1955-1957 (Folder 161)
    - Dupont, 1957-1958 (Folder 162)
    - Dupont, 1958-1959 (Folder 163)
    - Dupont, 1959-1960 (Folder 164)
    - Dupont, 1960-1961 (Folder 165)
    - Dupont, 1961-1962 (Folder 166)
    - Dupont, 1962-1963 (Folder 167)
    - Dupont, 1963-1966 (Folder 168)
    - Durante, 1951-1966 (Folder 169)
    - E, 1951-1966 (Folder 170)
    - Far-Fer, 1951-1966 (Folder 171)
    - Fin-Fis, 1951-1966 (Folder 172)
    - Fle-Fro, 1951-1966 (Folder 173)
    - Gaines, 1951-1966 (Folder 174)
    - Gam-Goo, 1951-1966 (Folder 175)
    - Goodman, 1951 (Folder 176)
    - Goodman, 1951 (Folder 177)
    - Goodman, 1951-1952 (Folder 178)
    - Goodman, 1952 (Folder 179)
    - Goodman, 1952-1954 (Folder 180)
    - Goodman, 1954-1955 (Folder 181)
    - Goodman, 1955-1962 (Folder 182)
    - Gou-Gre, 1951-1966 (Folder 183)
    - Gri-Gun, 1951-1966 (Folder 184)
    - Haefele, 1958-1959 (Folder 185)
    - Haefele, 1959-1960 (Folder 186)
    - Haefele, 1960-1961 (Folder 187)
    - Haefele, 1961 (Folder 188)
    - Haefele, 1961-1962 (Folder 189)
    - Haefele, 1962 (Folder 190)
    - Haefele, 1962 (Folder 191)
    - Haefele, 1962-1963 (Folder 192)
    - Haefele, 1963 (Folder 193)
    - Haefele, 1963-1964 (Folder 194)
    - Haefele, 1964 (Folder 195)
    - Haefele, 1965-1966 (Folder 196)
    - Hag-Har, 1951-1966 (Folder 197)
    - Harsch, 1952 (Folder 198)
    - Harsch, 1952-1954 (Folder 199)
    - Harsch, 1951-1966 (Folder 200)
    - Hayman, 1951-1966 (Folder 201)
    - Hazard, 1951-1966 (Folder 202)
    - Hei-Her, 1951-1966 (Folder 203)
    - Hol-Hyd, 1951-1966 (Folder 204)
    - J-L, 1951-1966 (Folder 205)
    - Mac-Mad, 1951-1966 (Folder 206)
    - Mag-McD, 1951-1966 (Folder 207)
    - McG-Mea, 1951-1966 (Folder 208)
    - Mil-Minn, 1951-1966 (Folder 209)
    - Minow, 1961-1963 (Folder 210)
    - Minow, 1964 (Folder 211)
    - Minow, 1964-1965 (Folder 212)
    - Mir-Mor, 1951-1966 (Folder 213)
    - Moses, 1964-1965 (Folder 214)
    - Moses, 1965 (Folder 215)
    - Mue-O, 1951-1966 (Folder 216)
    - Pac-Pan, 1951-1966 (Folder 217)
    - Pea-Pre, 1951-1966 (Folder 218)
    - Ren-Rub, 1951-1966 (Folder 219)
    - Russell, 1951-1966 (Folder 220)
    - Sar-Sci, 1951-1966 (Folder 221)
    - Sel-Sig, 1951-1966 (Folder 222)
    - Sko-Spe, 1951-1966 (Folder 223)
    - Spo-Stev, 1951-1966 (Folder 224)
    - Stew-Swa, 1951-1966 (Folder 225)
    - Taishoff, 1956-1959 (Folder 226)
    - Taishoff, 1959-1961 (Folder 227)
    - Taishoff, 1961-1962 (Folder 228)
    - Taishoff, 1962-1963 (Folder 229)
    - Taishoff, 1963-1964 (Folder 230)
    - Taishoff, 1964-1965 (Folder 231)
    - Taishoff, 1965-1966 (Folder 232)
    - Tay-Too, 1951-1966 (Folder 233)
    - Towle, 1951-1966 (Folder 234)
    - Wag-Whi, 1951-1966 (Folder 235)
    - Williams-Williamson, 1951-1966 (Folder 236)
    - Z, 1951-1966 (Folder 237)
    - Unknown/Multiple Authors/Recipients, 1951-1966 (Folder 238)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1952-1961 (Box 8, Folder 239-243)
    Items in this subseries relate to communications between the General Federation of Women's Clubs and Riegel as curator for the Dupont Awards. Most of the correspondence consists of requests by Riegel for the leadership of the G.F.W.C. to participate on the Committee of the Dupont Awards.
    - Ahl-Cha, 1951-1966 (Folder 239)
    - Gifford, 1951-1966 (Folder 240)
    - Har-McC, 1951-1966 (Folder 241)
    - Ozb-Pro, 1951-1966 (Folder 242)
    - Photos and Misc., 1951-1966 (Folder 243)
  - Judges, 1951-1966 (Box 9-10, Folder 244-320)
    Items in this sub-series consist of materials related to the judging of various Television stations, radio stations, and commentators for the Dupont Awards. Included are some judges' comments on different stations and correspondence about evaluating stations.
    - Background Info, 1951-1966 (Folder 244)
    - Ahl-Bat, 1951-1966 (Folder 245)
    - Bec-Bod, 1951-1966 (Folder 246)
    - Bro-Bys, 1951-1966 (Folder 247)
    - Cam-Can, 1951-1966 (Folder 248)
    - Carmichael, 1951-1966 (Folder 249)
    - Catledge, 1951-1966 (Folder 250)
    - Cha-Col, 1951-1966 (Folder 251)
    - Cor-Cox, 1951-1966 (Folder 252)
    - Dav-Don, 1951-1966 (Folder 253)
    - Dow-Dun, 1951-1966 (Folder 254)
    - Durr, 1960-1962 (Folder 255)
    - Durr, 1962-1963 (Folder 256)
    - Durr, 1963-1964 (Folder 257)
    - V.Durr-Dix, 1951-1966 (Folder 258)
    - E, 1951-1966 (Folder 259)
    - F, 1951-1966 (Folder 260)
    - Gai-Gol, 1951-1966 (Folder 261)
    - Goo-Guy, 1951-1966 (Folder 262)
    - Hae-Har, 1951-1966 (Folder 263)
    - Hea-Hur, 1951-1966 (Folder 264)
    - Hyde, 1951-1966 (Folder 265)
    - J-K, 1951-1966 (Folder 266)
    - Lam-Lan, 1951-1966 (Folder 267)
    - Laurent, 1961-1962 (Folder 268)
    - Laurent, 1962-1964 (Folder 269)
    - Laurent, 1964-1965 (Folder 270)
    - Laurent, 1965-1966 (Folder 271)
    - Law-Lew, 1951-1966 (Folder 272)
    - Linton, 1951-1966 (Folder 273)
    - Logan, 1951-1966 (Folder 274)
    - Loomis, 1951-1966 (Folder 275)
    - Lowry, 1959-1963 (Folder 276)
    - Lowry, 1963-1966 (Folder 277)
    - Mar-Mau, 1951-1966 (Folder 278)
    - McC-McD, 1951-1966 (Folder 279)
    - McK-Mos, 1951-1966 (Folder 280)
    - Mosse-Mye, 1951-1966 (Folder 281)
    - Naf-D.Nel, 1951-1966 (Folder 282)
    - H.Nel-Niv, 1951-1966 (Folder 283)
    - Pen-Pre, 1951-1966 (Folder 284)
    - Price, 1951-1966 (Folder 285)
    - R, 1951-1966 (Folder 286)
    - Sargent, 1951-1966 (Folder 287)
    - Sch-She, 1951-1966 (Folder 288)
    - Shulman, 1951-1966 (Folder 289)
    - Smith, 1951-1966 (Folder 290)
    - Sor-Ste, 1951-1966 (Folder 291)
    - Stuart, 1964-1965 (Folder 292)
    - Stuart, 1966 (Folder 293)
    - Sulzer, 1951-1966 (Folder 294)
    - Sum, 1951-1966 (Folder 295)
    - Tai-Tem, 1951-1966 (Folder 296)
    - Towle, 1960-1962 (Folder 297)
    - Towle, 1963-1965 (Folder 298)
    - Wil-K.Wright, 1951-1966 (Folder 299)
    - L.Wright-Wyn, 1951-1966 (Folder 300)